dlnowsoft.com 2019-07-12

# Privacy Policy

### Introduction

We at DLNow are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us. DLNow has established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information. For the purposes of this statement, "Personal Information" means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. 

### Information Collection

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information") or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you want to provide us with your personal data, to give us the opportunity to get in touch with you. 

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and your time spent at our sites, and to gather broad demographic information. This allows us to see which parts of our sites users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means, for instance, that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will remain anonymous. We do not use this information for any other purposes. 

### Use of personal information

DLNow does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on DLNow behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against DLNow policy to sell Personal Information collected online without consent. In short, DLNow does not sell registrant information to lists. In some cases, DLNow may use a visitor's personal information to understand overall patterns for site usage, to contact the user for clarification on inaccurate information, or to follow up on a customer service issue. Personal information may include name, address, telephone number, etc. 

### Links to other sites

This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that DLNow is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web Sites as well as any information they might collect, even though our name or logo may appear on those sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the Privacy Statements of each and every Web site that you visit, as the privacy policy of those sites may differ from ours. Our Privacy Statement applies solely to dlnowsoft.com. 

### Use of "cookies"

During your visit to our website, so-called "cookies" are saved to your computer. These "cookies" register information about the navigation of your computer on our website (loaded pages, date, time of day and length of visit etc.) which we can access during your next visit in order to adapt the website to your personal requirements and optimize loading times. We also use this information to enter your data into enquiry forms and suchlike so that you do not need to fill them in yourself again and again. We never store passwords or similarly sensitive data in cookies. The use of cookies is common and advantageous. Cookies are used on most larger websites. By indicating how and when visitors use a website, cookies aid us in finding out which areas are popular and which areas are not. Many improvements and updates are based on information supplied by cookies. Cookies can also help us to personalize web content and meet the desires of our visitors. Our website does not use cookies to collect personal information from your computer that was not initially sent as a cookie. You have the option to control the acceptance of cookies yourself and, if you wish, to block them entirely by configuring your browser as follows. 

### Children's Privacy

Our website is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age. 

### Your Consent

By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to DLNow's processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time.
